

Masakhiro Gerelt

Web Application Developer

Q Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia Chingeltei district 3-rd khoroo 2nd-40000 street apartment 13-53, Ulaanbaatar, 15172, Mongolia yuugen0506@gmail.com +97699718822

Profile

I'm a Full Stack Developer with over 6 years of experience. I'm from Mongolia. I was born on May 6, 1993, in Ulaanbaatar and am half Japanese. I have had many friends since I was young and I am a communicative and loyal person who does not betray people's trust. I am a quick learner and I like to follow a clean sequence in my work. I have studied and lived in Ireland as well as Japan.

Employment History

2019 - 2024

Web Application Developer at Ber Solution

Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia

Senior Full Stack developer.

2017 - 2018

Tokyo Japan

Assistant programmer & electrical engineer assistant at ITC Consulting

- Fixing software bugs for smooth operation.
- Developing and maintaining websites using scripting languages.
- Setting up and managing databases efficiently.
- Installing and configuring software setups on machines.
- Collaborating with team members for technical optimization.

2016 - 2017

Osaka, Japan

Assistant programmer & learner at SUNSYSTEM

- Learning VB.NET & Visual Basic.
- Make some Databases & personal information programs.
- · Testing Programs.

Education

2011 - 2015

Soyol-Erdem

Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia

Bachelor

Programist

Details

Date / Place of birth

1993/05/06 Ulaanbaatar

Nationality

Mongolian

Driving license

A, B

Links

Facebook

Instagram

Skills

Laravel

CodeIgniter

WordPress

Django

Flask

DHI

Python

C#

JavaScript

HTML5

CSS3

SASS

• • • • • • • •

jQuery

• • • • • • •

2010 - 2011

Workers vocational

Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia

High school education

2008 - 2010

Saint Paul's

Dublin, Ireland

High school education

2006 - 2008

King's Kids

Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia

High school education

2000 - 2006

Sant

Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia

High school education

Projects

Web application:

Purchase Order System

We developed an admin panel platform for managing purchase orders for Elogit clients. The platform also facilitates client management and access control.

For more information about the application, please visit https://elpos.e-logit.com.

The system was ordered by the client. For additional details, please visit https://ec-bpo.e-logit.com.

Web application:

HUB Goyo Travel

We developed an admin panel platform for managing clients, trips, itinerary, invoices, tasks, camp vouchers, and post-payment systems. Additionally, the platform includes a booking system for clients.

For more information about the application, please visit https://hub.goyotravel.com.

Web:

Goyo Travel

We developed a platform for group tours, private tailor-made trips, and selected additional travel services to and within Mongolia.

For more information about the application, please visit https://www.goyotravel.com.

Api

Back-End:

We developed an API to retrieve a list of orders and generate CSV files from those orders. The API is used to fetch data from the following shops: VueJs
React
TypeScript
VB.NET
REST
Apache
Nginx
Websocket
MySQL

Languages

.

MongoDB

Oracle

Japanese

English

Mongolian

Hobbies

Basketball, Swimming, Cyber sport, Snowboard, Martial arts, Bodybuilding

- IIII. For more information about the shop, please visit https://www.ato-barai.com.
- Cross Mall. For more information about the shop, please visit https://cross-mall.jp.
- DSKIIII. For more information about the shop, please visit https://www.dsk-atobarai.jp.
- ebisumart. For more information about the shop, please visit https://www.ebisumart.com.
- ecforce. For more information about the shop, please visit https://ec-force.com.
- ectencho. For more information about the shop, please visit https://www.ec-tencho.jp.
- futureshop. For more information about the shop, please visit https://www.future-shop.jp.
- jaccs. For more information about the shop, please visit https://www.jaccs.co.jp/en/corporate.
- kuroneko. For more information about the shop, please visit
 - https://www.kuronekoyamato.co.jp/ytc/en/send/preparations/payoff.
- Rakuten. For more information about the shop, please visit https://www.rakuten.co.jp.
- Shopify. For more information about the shop, please visit https://www.shopify.com.
- ShopServe. For more information about the shop, please visit https://shopserve.in/collections/all.